socialenterpriselive.com 2009-11-11

# Privacy Policy | Social Enterprise

By accessing or using this website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. London Fields Publishing Ltd (“We”), publishers of Social Enterprise magazine, are committed to respecting the privacy of users entering this site and we recognise the importance of the responsible use of information collected on this site. The purpose of this policy therefore is to explain to you the nature of the information we record and store about you and the way in which it is used. We reserve the right to alter the policy from time to time at our sole discretion.

## Data Protection Act 1998

The Data Protection Act defines the legal responsibilities of data users such as Make A Difference Publishing Ltd. The Act governs the collection, storage, use and transfer of personal data, for example, name, address, email, age, etc.

## Accuracy

We will do our best to maintain the accuracy of the personal information you supply to us. You have the right to access and correct your personal information at any time.

If you wish to do so please contact us at [info@socialenterpriselive.co.uk](mailto:info@socialenterpriselive.com). We may charge a fee for this service.

## Sharing your Data

We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.

No financial data submitted will be stored.

## Further Information

Our site may be linked to other relevant websites and where this is the case, this Privacy Policy will not apply to those other sites once you have entered them. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of other websites.

## Feedback

On our website we may provide space for your comments and/or provide a short survey for you to complete. Personal information that you provide to us in those sections of the website is only used to inform our future actions in the areas surveyed. It is not re-used or re-applied for any other purpose.

If you contact us via our website the contact details that you provide us with will be kept for as long as is necessary to enable us to deal with your query.

## Cookies

We may track your visit to our site by giving you a cookie when you enter. Cookies are pieces of information sent to your browser on a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive for record keeping purposes. We use Cookies to make visiting our site easier. Cookies allow us to save passwords for you so that you will not have to re-enter them the next time you visit. Cookies cannot be used to obtain other information from your hard disk. The Cookie is used to collect statistical information and is not used to identify individuals.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept Cookies. If you prefer you can reset your browser either to notify you when you have received a Cookie or to refuse to accept Cookies.

It is important to note that if you choose not accept Cookies, or you set your browser not to accept Cookies, you may not be able to use certain features on our site.

## Aggregate Data

In general, our service automatically gathers certain usage information about the numbers and frequency of visitors to our website. We only use such data in aggregated form and do not identify you individually. This collected data helps us to determine how much our customers use parts of the site, so we can improve our site for your use.

## IP Address

We may collect and track traffic by IP address. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer when you use your browser on the internet. We log this information, but this information is never linked to any personally identifying information. It is used to audit the number of visitors coming to our website.

## Privacy Policy Changes

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.

## Export of Your Data Outside the European Economic Area

Because the Internet infrastructure is global, and it is not possible to predict the routes that information sent over the Internet will take, the information you provide may be transferred temporarily via a route which takes it outside the European Economic Area as it passes between you and us. By submitting your information to us you consent to this transfer.
